<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mi Sitio</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mi Sitio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es-es</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:17:31 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bienvenido a Hugo</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/bienvenido-a-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:17:31 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/bienvenido-a-hugo/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido a Hugo Features  Import a HTML file and watch it magically convert to Markdown Drag and drop images (requires your Dropbox account be linked) Import and save files from GitHub, Dropbox, Google Drive and One Drive Drag and drop markdown and HTML files into Dillinger Export documents as Markdown, HTML and PDF  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mi Primer Posts</title>
      <link>http://example.org/posts/mi-primer-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 20:16:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/posts/mi-primer-posts/</guid>
      <description>Mi Primer Post Tech Dillinger uses a number of open source projects to work properly:
 [AngularJS] - HTML enhanced for web apps! [Ace Editor] - awesome web-based text editor [markdown-it] - Markdown parser done right. Fast and easy to extend. [Twitter Bootstrap] - great UI boilerplate for modern web apps [node.js] - evented I/O for the backend [Express] - fast node.js network app framework [@tjholowaychuk] [Gulp] - the streaming build system Breakdance - HTML to Markdown converter [jQuery] - duh  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contacto</title>
      <link>http://example.org/contacto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:36:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/contacto/</guid>
      <description>Consequat dolor nisi nostrud consectetur sunt officia officia. Pariatur id sint velit esse ullamco velit in culpa eu. Ut qui nostrud eiusmod deserunt ut et dolor do laborum aliqua incididunt magna velit. Proident anim ex culpa occaecat laborum. Quis sunt aliqua aliqua esse officia duis eu aliqua proident non. Proident deserunt laboris consectetur pariatur anim officia. Esse aliqua incididunt adipisicing magna velit quis sunt pariatur commodo reprehenderit nisi. Est amet adipisicing ut mollit amet deserunt proident quis est incididunt pariatur deserunt.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
